https://www.prb.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Skip to content
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy covers the Population Reference Bureau’s treatment of personally identifiable information that PRB collects when you are on the PRB sites and when you use PRB’s services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that PRB does not own or control or to people that PRB does not employ or manage.
Protecting your privacy and your information is a top priority at PRB. We have taken careful measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information. Once we receive the information that you enter into our website, it is stored behind a firewall. PRB employees are made aware of our privacy and security policies through our Employee Handbook. PRB shares personally identifiable information with employees who need it in order to perform their jobs. PRB will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. PRB may send personally identifiable information about you to other organizations or people when:
We have your consent to share the information.
We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested.
We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of PRB to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.)
We are responding to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process.
Personal information that PRB collects includes your name, home and work phone numbers, address, e-mail address, and credit card information if you order publications from PRB.
PRB maintains electronic newsletters that you may subscribe or unsubscribe to at any time.
The PRB website does use “cookies.” Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to allow you to navigate between different functional sections of our website without having to log in with every new page. The “Help” button on the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of the website’s richest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to PRB’s cookies.
PRB gives you the ability to review and edit any personally identifiable information that PRB has stored on its websites. Please note that any information that we have copied may remain in back-up storage for some period of time after your deletion request. This may be the case even though no information about your account remains in our active user databases.
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using software that encrypts information you input. PRB uses industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions. We do transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. We do not store your credit card information in our database.
Please protect yourself against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.
